https://www.girosole.com/privacy/

Choose a region
Abruzzo  (1)
Basilicata  (2)
Calabria  (1)
Campania  (3)
Chianti  (1)
Lazio  (1)
Liguria  (2)
Lombardia  (2)
Marche  (1)
Molise  (1)
Piemonte  (4)
Puglia  (2)
Sicilia  (3)
Toscana  (10)
Trentino Alto Adige  (1)
Umbria  (4)
Val d'Aosta  (1)
Veneto  (1)
Interests and activities
Antiquity  (18)
Cooking  (12)
Food  (10)
Harvests  (1)
Hiking  (6)
Hilltowns  (5)
History  (12)
Walking  (14)
Wine  (7)
Wineries  (11)
Landscapes
Countryside  (23)
Lakeside  (2)
Mountains  (7)
Seaside  (11)
What kind of tour?
Guided walks(24)Self-guided trip(12)
Privacy Policy
What personally identifiable information is collected from you?
GIROSOLE collects information in several ways from different parts of our web site.
Some personal information is gathered when you request information from us. At this time, we ask for your name and email address. These items are required in order to be able to answer your inquiry. If you would like for us to respond to your inquiry by telephone, you can also provide your telephone number.
We also ask you for personal information when you book a tour with us through our on-line booking form.
Finally, we ask for your name and email address if you wish to subscribe to our newsletter.
Use of Cookies
Anonymous information about your use of this site is shared with Google and Statcounter via cookies so we can understand our site’s traffic and thus better serve our site’s visitors. This is nonpersonal information.
Every page within the site on which we ask you for personal information includes a link to this Privacy Policy.
How is your information used?
The goal of GIROSOLE in collecting personal information is to respond to your requests for information about our tours, or to help you book one of our tours. We also send an occasional newsletter to subscribers for which all cancellation requests are immediately honored.
When you book a tour with us and if you wish to pay by credit card, you will do so through our secure payment gateway with Stripe.com. Neither we nor Stripe retains any of your credit card information.
With whom is your information shared?
GIROSOLE does not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when you request us to make hotel reservations for you before or after your tour with us.
GIROSOLE does not and will never sell or rent your information to any third party.
What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information?
If you prefer not to provide your email address or phone number when requesting information from us, we will not be able to answer your inquiry. You are free to use the rest of the GIROSOLE site as you wish within limits of our copyright notice at the bottom of every page. When we send you our newsletter, you can opt out of receiving further newsletter by simply clicking on the unsubscribe link. Your information will be deleted, and you will not receive any further emails from us.
How can you access, update or delete your information?
Please contact us if you wish to update or delete any information we may have about you. Your request will be honored upon receipt.
Why Girosole
Why Girosole
Terrific Testimonials
Superlative Support
Fantabulous Food
Amazing Activities
Awesome Accommodations
Genuinely Great Guides
The GIROSOLE Team
Request more info
"...the perfect combination..."
We had a marvelous trip, and much of it was due to the planning that went into the Girosole itinerary – it was the perfect combination of walking, scenery, history, culture, time spent with the group, and time to explore on our own. I can’t imagine a better way to see the Amalfi coast. Our guide Ulisse was very friendly and helpful – he did a wonderful job of keeping us organized, giving us the history of the area, and providing advice on things to do when we were on our own. We would like to travel again with Girosole (maybe Tuscany next time) and will certainly recommend the walking tours to all of our friends.
Christie and Bill Waters
Girosole
Find a trip
Guided Walks
Valle d’Aosta’s Gran Paradiso
Piedmont’s Langhe District
Piedmont Cooking and Walking
Italian Lakes
Abruzzo  (1)
Basilicata  (2)
Calabria  (1)
Campania  (3)
Chianti  (1)
Lazio  (1)
Liguria  (2)
Lombardia  (2)
Marche  (1)
Molise  (1)
Piemonte  (4)
Puglia  (2)
Sicilia  (3)
Toscana  (10)
Trentino Alto Adige  (1)
Umbria  (4)
Val d'Aosta  (1)
Veneto  (1)
Interests and activities
Antiquity  (18)
Cooking  (12)
Food  (10)
Harvests  (1)
Hiking  (6)
Hilltowns  (5)
History  (12)
Walking  (14)
Wine  (7)
Wineries  (11)
Landscapes
Countryside  (23)
Lakeside  (2)
Mountains  (7)
Seaside  (11)
What kind of tour?
Guided walks(24)Self-guided trip(12)
Why Girosole
Book a trip
Blog
Contact us
